[{"answer": "And while he tries to form the question, I'll tell you who's with me tonight.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "I don't -- really?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "I went to a Jewish high school, gloom.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Not at all?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "We don't have any Jews at McKinley High.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Yes, the teachers say, yes, you can sing, but you're Jewish, go to work, learn, you know?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Right, right.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "I love how you say I looked down and there was a great bunny slipper and you say, why -- why is my bunny slippers so gray?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I didn't.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Did you pay?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Do we understand each other?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Robin Williams is --", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "And you look at Robin Williams, you know?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Yes, I say actress, too.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What's so terrible?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "So are you into politics?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "First of all, the joke is, the Obamas are the white person -- people now.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Why do you hate it?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Didn't you say in your movie Jack Lemon walked out once?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "One of your first roles you played a lesbian in the '50s in a play and you're in love with Barbra Streisand?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Pre-\"Funny Girl.\"", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "This is -- yes, pre-\"Funny Girl,\" right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "IVERS: Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "The two of you?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Yes, that was -- she went through the gift thing and like took everything.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Was that great?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Smack on the lips.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "And you kissed her?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Isn't that something?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I have done a lot of understudying where you're kind of -- you're kind of get there in the right place at the right time kind of accidentally.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "If I was to use her, who's going to watch?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What do you want?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "That's because you love the craft.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "I will take anything, you know?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I work at the West Bank --", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "You still do?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "You look great.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Does it hurt your feelings, too?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "It affects your self-esteem?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "What self-esteem?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Do you have a twin brother?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "See?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "On important days I have someone comes over.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "And you do it yourself or do you have someone come over?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Well, Joan, coming up soon, we're going to be speaking of is this yours, Melissa Rivers, yours --", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Is it yours?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Once I had a boss come in and say oh, I had a sex dream about you last night.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "What kinds of conduct, verbal conduct might be problematic?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I'm not telling you.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "Who was it?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "The point was --", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Was it Oprah?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "I didn't really have a choice.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "YNCH: How does it make you feel to know that everybody witnessed that humiliation?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "I don't know any other way.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Are you as compelled as your mother?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "I call mine the career.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "That date book of yours is full now, isn't it?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "That's a good one.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "How many times?", "qSentId": 881}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 888, "question": "Have you been in love after?", "qSentId": 887}, {"answer": "-- your father.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 890, "question": "Could you keep that to yourself?", "qSentId": 889}, {"answer": "We were together until -- about 10 and a half years and then he cheated on me.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 898, "question": "How long were you together?", "qSentId": 897}, {"answer": "At that age, an old guy --", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 900, "question": "That was it?", "qSentId": 899}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 906, "question": "Have you ever been in love?", "qSentId": 905}, {"answer": "When we met, yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "Were you in love with your ex-husband?", "qSentId": 916}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 922, "question": "Is he an active father?", "qSentId": 921}, {"answer": "Well, he who predicts -- he who looks into the crystal ball in this cycle ends up eating glass, as we say.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 984, "question": "What do you think is going to go down for the Republicans in this primary?", "qSentId": 983}, {"answer": "First, let me say, I never had grits until I moved down here.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 1014, "question": "Do you think that if he becomes the nominee -- and it looks like he probably will -- that the party will be able to unify around him, that there will be some energy and some wind at his back coming into the general election?", "qSentId": 1013}, {"answer": "Yes, we call it a cosmetology license, and I'm very good.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 1083, "question": "Is that true, Mary Matalin?", "qSentId": 1082}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- obviously it's overwhelming, it's wild, crazy.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 1133, "question": "How does it feel to be the most famous person in Grand Forks, North Dakota?", "qSentId": 1132}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 1159, "question": "Maybe in the summer?", "qSentId": 1158}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 1163, "question": "What was your response?", "qSentId": 1162}, {"answer": "I sure have.", "docId": "120312pmt", "aSentId": 1194, "question": "Have you ever been to an Olive Garden?", "qSentId": 1193}]